Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - Georgia Tech, 1979 November 03
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1979 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1161)
  - Wake Forest, 1979 November 10
    Duke loss, score: 14-17
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1979 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1162)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1979 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1163)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1979 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1164)
  - NC State, 1979 November 17
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1165)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1166)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1167)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1979 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1168)
  - North Carolina, 1979 November 24
    Duke loss, score: 16-37
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: First Quarter, 1979 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1169)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Second Quarter, 1979 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1170)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Third Quarter, 1979 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1171)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1979 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1172)
  - East Carolina, 1980 September 06
    Duke loss, score: 10-35
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Offense 1, 1980 September 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1173)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Offense 2, 1980 September 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1174)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Defense 1, 1980 September 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1175)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Defense 2, 1980 September 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1176)
  - Auburn, 1980 September 20
    Duke loss, score: 28-35
    - Duke vs. Auburn: First Quarter, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1177)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Second Quarter, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1178)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Third Quarter, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1179)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Fourth Quarter, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1180)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Defense 1, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1181)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Defense 2, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1182)
    - Duke vs. Auburn: Offense 1, 1980 September 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1183)
  - Virginia, 1980 September 27
    Duke loss, score: 17-20
    - Duke vs. Virginia: First Quarter, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1184)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Second Quarter, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1185)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Third Quarter, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1186)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Fourth Quarter, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1187)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1188)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1189)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1190)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1980 September 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1191)
  - Indiana, 1980 October 04
    Duke loss, score: 21-31
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 1, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1192)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 2, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1193)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Offense 1, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1194)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Offense 2, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1195)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: First Quarter, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1196)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Second Quarter, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1197)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Third Quarter, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1198)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Fourth Quarter, 1980 October 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1199)
  - South Carolina, 1980 October 11
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: First Quarter, 1980 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1200)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Second Quarter, 1980 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1201)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Third Quarter, 1980 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1202)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Fourth Quarter, 1980 October 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1203)
  - Clemson, 1980 October 18
    Duke win, score: 34-17
    - Duke vs. Clemson: First Quarter, 1980 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1204)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Second Quarter, 1980 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1205)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Third Quarter, 1980 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 10, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1206)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Fourth Quarter, 1980 October 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1207)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Unknown game film coverage, 1980 October 18; DVD
  - Maryland, 1980 October 25
    - Duke vs. Maryland: First Quarter, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1208)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Second Quarter, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1209)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Third Quarter, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1210)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Fourth Quarter, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1211)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 1, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1212)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 2, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1213)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 1, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1214)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 2, 1980 October 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1215)
  - Georgia Tech, 1980 November 01
    Duke win, score: 17-12
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: First Quarter, 1980 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1216)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Second Quarter, 1980 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1217)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Third Quarter, 1980 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1218)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Fourth Quarter, 1980 November 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1219)
  - Wake Forest, 1980 November 08
    Duke loss, score: 24-27
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: First Quarter, 1980 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1220)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Second Quarter, 1980 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1221)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Third Quarter, 1980 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1222)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Fourth Quarter, 1980 November 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1223)
  - NC State, 1980 November 15
    Duke loss, score: 21-38
    - Duke vs. NC State: First Quarter, 1980 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1224)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Second Quarter, 1980 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1225)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Third Quarter, 1980 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1226)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Fourth Quarter, 1980 November 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 9, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1227)
  - Ohio State, 1981 September 12
    Duke loss, score: 13-34
    - Duke vs. Ohio State: Offense 1, 1981 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1228)
    - Duke vs. Ohio State: Offense 2, 1981 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1229)
    - Duke vs. Ohio State: Defense 1, 1981 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1230)
    - Duke vs. Ohio State: Defense 2, 1981 September 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1231)
  - South Carolina, 1981 September 19
    Duke loss, score: 3-17
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1981 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1232)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1981 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1233)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 1, 1981 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1234)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 2, 1981 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1235)
  - Virginia, 1981 September 26
    Duke win, score: 29-24
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1981 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1236)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1981 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1237)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1981 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1238)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1981 September 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1239)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unknown game film coverage, 1981 September 26; DVD
  - East Carolina, 1981 October 03
    Duke win, score: 24-14
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Offense 1, 1981 October 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1240)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Offense 2, 1981 October 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1241)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Defense 1, 1981 October 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1242)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Defense 2, 1981 October 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1243)
  - Virginia Tech, 1981 October 10
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Offense 1, 1981 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1244)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Offense 2, 1981 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1245)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 1, 1981 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1246)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 2, 1981 October 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1247)
  - Clemson, 1981 October 17
    Duke loss, score: 10-38
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 1, 1981 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1248)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 2, 1981 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1249)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1, 1981 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1250)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 2, 1981 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1251)
  - Maryland, 1981 October 24
    Duke loss, score: 21-24
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 1, 1981 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1252)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 2, 1981 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1253)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 1, 1981 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1254)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 2, 1981 October 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1255)
  - Georgia Tech, 1981 October 31
    Duke win, score: 38-24
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1981 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1256)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1981 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1257)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1981 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1258)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1981 October 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 12, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1259)
  - Wake Forest, 1981 November 07
    Duke win, score: 31-10
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1981 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1260)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1981 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1261)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1981 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1262)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 2, 1981 November 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1263)
  - NC State, 1981 November 14
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1981 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1264)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1981 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1265)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1981 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1266)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1981 November 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 14, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1267)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unknown game film coverage, 1981 November 14; DVD
  - North Carolina, 1981 November 21
    Duke loss, score: 10-31
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1981 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1268)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1981 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1269)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1981 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1270)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1981 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 13, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1271)
  - Indiana, 1983 September 10
    Duke loss, score: 10-15
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 1, 1983 September 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1272)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 2, 1983 September 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1273)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Offense 2, 1983 September 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1274)
  - South Carolina, 1983 September 17
    Duke loss, score: 24-30
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 1, 1983 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1275)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 2, 1983 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1276)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1983 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1277)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1983 September 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1278)
  - Miami, 1983 October 01
    Duke loss, score: 17-56
    - Duke vs. Miami: Defense 2, 1983 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1279)
    - Duke vs. Miami: Defense 1, 1983 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1280)
  - Virginia Tech, 1983 October 08
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 1, 1983 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1281)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 2, 1983 October 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1282)
  - Maryland, 1983 October 22
    Duke loss, score: 3-38
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 1, 1983 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1283)
      Color film
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 2, 1983 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1284)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Defense 1, 1983 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1285)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Offense 2, 1983 October 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1286)
  - Georgia Tech, 1983 October 29
    Duke win, score: 32-26
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1983 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1287)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1983 October 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1288)
  - NC State, 1983 November 10
    Duke win, score: 27-26
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1983 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1289)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1983 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1290)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1983 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1291)
  - North Carolina, 1983 November 19
    Duke loss, score: 27-34
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1983 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1292)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1983 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1293)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1983 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1294)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1983 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1295)
  - Indiana, 1984 September 08
    Duke win, score: 31-24
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Offense 1, 1984 September 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1296)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Offense 2, 1984 September 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1297)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 1, 1984 September 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1298)
    - Duke vs. Indiana: Defense 2, 1984 September 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1299)
  - South Carolina, 1984 September 22
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 1, 1984 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1300)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Offense 2, 1984 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1301)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 1, 1984 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1302)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Defense 2, 1984 September 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 16, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1303)
  - Army, 1984 September 29
    Duke loss, score: 9-13
    - Duke vs. Army: Offense 1, 1984 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1304)
    - Duke vs. Army: Offense 2, 1984 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1305)
    - Duke vs. Army: Defense 1, 1984 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1306)
    - Duke vs. Army: Defense 2, 1984 September 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1307)
  - Virginia, 1984 October 06
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 1, 1984 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1308)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Defense 2, 1984 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1309)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 1, 1984 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1310)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Offense 2, 1984 October 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 15, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1311)
  - Virginia Tech, 1984 October 13
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 1, 1984 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1312)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Offense 1, 1984 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1313)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Defense 2, 1984 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1314)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Offense 2, 1984 October 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1315)
  - Clemson, 1984 October 20
    Duke loss, score: 21-54
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 1, 1984 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1316)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Offense 2, 1984 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1317)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 1, 1984 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1318)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Defense 2, 1984 October 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1319)
  - Georgia Tech, 1984 November 03
    Duke loss, score: 3-31
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 1, 1984 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1320)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Defense 2, 1984 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1321)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 1, 1984 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1322)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Offense 2, 1984 November 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1323)
  - Wake Forest, 1984 November 10
    Duke loss, score: 16-20
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 1, 1984 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1324)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Defense 2, 1984 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1325)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 1, 1984 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1326)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Offense 2, 1984 November 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1327)
  - NC State, 1984 November 17
    Duke win, score: 16-13
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 1, 1984 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1328)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 1, 1984 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1329)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Defense 2, 1984 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1330)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Offense 2, 1984 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 17, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1331)
  - North Carolina, 1984 November 24
    Duke loss, score: 15-17
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 1, 1984 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1332)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Defense 2, 1984 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1333)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 1, 1984 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1334)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Offense 2, 1984 November 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1335)
  - Northwestern, 1985 September 07
    Duke win, score: 40-17
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Offense 1, 1985 September 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1336)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Offense 2, 1985 September 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1337)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Defense 1, 1985 September 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1338)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Defense 2, 1985 September 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1339)
  - Ohio, 1985 September 21
    Duke win, score: 34-13
    - Duke vs. Ohio: Defense 2, 1985 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1340)
    - Duke vs. Ohio: Offense 1, 1985 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1341)
    - Duke vs. Ohio: Offense 2, 1985 September 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-1342)